Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs
1894-circa 1992, undated
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation
O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986
Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946
Bry, Doris, 1920-2014
Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979
Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923
Hamilton, Juan, b. 1945
Langton, Basil, 1912-2003
Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001
Newman, Arnold, 1918-2006
Porter, Eliot Furness, 1909-1990
Varon, Malcolm
MS.57
14.167 Linear Feet
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains hundreds of photographs related to Georgia O'Keeffe.
Photographs; Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation
- Maria Rapp Boursault and Her daughter with Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1918; 2006.6.10; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Reprint From Van Deren Coke Print by Alfred Stieglitz Photograph - Marie Rapp Boursalt, her daughter, and Georgia O'Keeffe, Lake George 1918
  General
  Georgia O'Keeffe and Maria Rapp Boursault in swimsuits at Lake George.
  https://rightsstatements.org/page/1.0/?language=en
  Public Domain
  Photographs
- Georgia O'Keeffe, Fred and Ella Varnum, and Bly with Judith, Lake George, circa 1920; 2006.6.11; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 7 7/8 x 10 inches; See AS Appendix no. 21Handwritten on verso: The number 1, circled
  Probably photographed during the move from Oaklawn, house on the shore of Lake George, to a farmhouse on the same property. The sculpture, Judith, is by Moses Ezekiel.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1932; 2006.6.13; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Film transparency 3 x 4 1/4 inches; gelatin silver print 9 1/4 x 6 3/4
  Photographic film
- A Street in Bellagio, 1894; 2006.6.14; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; copy of National Gallery of Art print.Two Labels on Verso: "NO IMAGE MAY BE CROPPED OR ALTERED IN ANY WAY WHATSOEVER. NO TYPE MAY BE SUPERIMPOSED ON ANY IMAGE." "Alfred Stieglitz, A Street in Bellagio.1894 Platinum print, 199 x 148 mm ( 7 7/8 x 5 3/4 "), National Gallery of Art, Alfred Stieglitz Collection
- From My Window At An American Place, North, 1931; 2006.6.15; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; copy of National Gallery of Art print. See AS 1377Two Labels on Verso: "NO IMAGE MAY BE CROPPED OR ALTERED IN ANY WAY WHATSOEVER. NO TYPE MAY BE SUPERIMPOSED ON ANY IMAGE." "Alfred Stieglitz, From My Window At An American Place, North, 1931. gelatin silver print, 241 x 193 mm ( 9 1/2 x 7 5/8 "), National Gallery of Art, Alfred Stieglitz Collection
- The Ferry Boat, 1920s-1930s; 2006.6.16; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 8 x 9 7/8 inches; copy of National Gallery of Art print.Two Labels on Verso: "NO IMAGE MAY BE CROPPED OR ALTERED IN ANY WAY WHATSOEVER. NO TYPE MAY BE SUPERIMPOSED ON ANY IMAGE." "Alfred Stieglitz, Untitled - The Ferry Boat, 1910 (?). gelatin silver print, 1920's or 1930's, 119 x 91 mm ( 4 5/8 x 3 1/2 "), National Gallery of Art, Alfred Stieglitz Collection
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Two Unidentified Women, 1950; 2006.6.106; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Back has a stamp: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company Oct. 23, 1950Stamp on verso: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company…Oct. 23, 1950
  Probably photographed in New Mexico.
  Copyright Not Evaluated
- Unidentified Woman, 1950; 2006.6.107; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Back has a stamp: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company Oct. 23, 1950Stamp on verso: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company…Oct. 23, 1950
- Ghost Ranch, 1950; 2006.6.108; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Back has a stamp: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company Sept. 11, 1950Stamp on verso: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company…Sept. 11, 1950
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Unidentified Women, 1950; 2006.6.109; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Back has a stamp: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company Oct. 23, 1950Stamp on verso: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company…Oct. 23, 1950
- Unidentified Woman, 1950; 2006.6.110; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Back has a stamp: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company Oct. 23, 1950Stamp on verso: This is a Kodacolor print. Made by Eastman Kodak Company…Oct. 23, 1950
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Chow, 1972; 2006.6.111; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Kodak stamp; May 24, 1972; JingoStamp on verso: Kodak June 72; Other stamp May 24, 1972; handwritten on verso: '1972 File (misc.) from: Paul C. Kasper Landscape architect California'
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Chow, 1972; 2006.6.112; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Kodak stamp; May 24, 1972; JingoStamp on verso: Kodak June 72; other stamp May 24, 1972
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Chow, 1972; 2006.6.113; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic 5 1/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Kodak stamp; May 24, 1972; JingoStamp on verso: Kodak June 72; other stamp May 24, 1972
  View of O'Keeffe's chow on portal at Ghost Ranch; flagstone, vigas, chamisa, assortment of rocks and bones on banco and wooden bench in background
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Unidentified Woman, 1972; 2006.6.114; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Kodak stamp; May 24, 1972Stamp on verso: Kodak June 72; other stamp May 24, 1972
  Unidentified woman is possibly Mrs. Kasper.
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Philip Sills, 1970; 2006.6.115; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Philip and Helen Silk'. Slightly wrinkled on the top centerHandwritten on verso: 'Philip and Helen Silk'
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Mr. Wu, 1960; 2006.6.116; Woodruff, Helen, 1899-1980; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; Kodacolor print, Kodak stamp. December 1960. Handwritten on verso: 3. 'Taipei. You and Wu.'Stamp on verso: Kodak December 60, Kodacolor print; Handwritten on verso: '3. Taipei. You and Wu.'
- Georgia O'Keeffe, Unidentified Woman and Claudia O'Keeffe, circa 1976-1981; 2006.6.117; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 7/16 x 5 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp and date August 1976. Two small pin holes.Stamp on verso: Kodak Aug 76
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Helen Woodruff in Asia, 1959 or 1960; 2006.6.118; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 13/16 x 4 7/8 inches
- Ghost Ranch House, 1964; 2006.6.119; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp and date July 1964. Handwritten on verso: 'From an ectachrom slide, in which the reflection was quite good.'Stamp on verso: Kodak Jul 64, Kodachrome print. Handwritten on verso: 'From an ektachrome slide, in which the reflection was quite good.'
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Kitchen, 1964; 2006.6.120; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Sitting in Breakfast Room, 1964; 2006.6.121; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Kitchen, 1964; 2006.6.122; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 9/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Walking Outdoors, 1964; 2006.6.123; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 9/16 inches
- Mrs. Lestz, Mrs. Lestz's Aunt, and Georgia O'Keeffe at Abiquiu House, 1972; 2006.6.124; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp with date July 1972Stamp on verso: Kodak Apr 72
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Doorway at Abiquiu House, 1972; 2006.6.125; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 1/16 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp with date July 1972
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Doorway at Abiquiu House, 1972; 2006.6.126; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 3 1/2 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp with date July 1972
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Juan Hamilton, after 1973; 2006.6.127; O'Keeffe, Claudia, 1899-1984; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 4 3/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Claudia O'K'Handwritten on verso: 'Claudia O'K.'
- Ruby Reid and Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.128; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Ted Reid'Handwritten on verso: 'Ted Reid'
- Ted Reid and Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.129; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 3/8 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stampStamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977
- Ruby Reid and Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.130; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 3/8 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stampStamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Desk at Ghost Ranch House, 1977; 2006.6.131; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 7/16 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stamp. Handwritten: 'This good of you.' Envelope in which pictures sent. Has Ted Reid Address and O'Keeffe.Stamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977. Handwritten: 'This is good of you.' Envelope in which pictures sent has Ted Reid Address and O'Keeffe.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, 1977; 2006.6.132; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 5/16 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stampStamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977; paper clip indent recto on top left, black ink smuges on top
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, 1977; 2006.6.133; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 5/16 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stampStamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Ghost Ranch House, 1977; 2006.6.134; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 7/16 inches; Verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977 stampStamp on verso: Foxprint Fox Photo July 1977
- Ted Reid and Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.135; 1 Photographic Prints negative
- Ted Reid and Georgia O'Keeffe, 1977; 2006.6.136; 1 Photographic Prints negative
- Sculpture, Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.137; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 11/16 x 3 3/16 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic & "Velox"
- Unidentified Family in Front of Sculpture in Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.138; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 5/8 x 3 13/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'My husband and my son and daughter'Handwritten on recto: two "X's" marking the children. Handwritten on verso: 'My husband and my son and daughter'
- Unidentified Family in Front of Sculpture in Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.139; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/4 x 2 5/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'My family and myself at 1950 in Persepolis'Handwritten on verso: 'My family and myself at 1950 in Persepolis'
- Sculpture, Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.140; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/4 x 2 1/2 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.141; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 3 7/8 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.142; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 3 7/8 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Ruins, Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.143; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 5/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Ruins, Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.144; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 5/8x 3 11/16 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Ruins, Persepolis, Iran, 1950; 2006.6.145; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 5/8 x 3 13/16 inches; Verso: Handwriting in ArabicHandwritten on verso: Arabic
- Esther Johnson with Baby, 1962; 2006.6.146; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 2 1/16 x 2 13/16 inches; Verso: Kodak stamp with date 1962Stamp on verso: Kodak Dec 62, Kodacolor Print
- Genevieve Roach, circa 1965; 2006.6.147; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'trusty steed, bed, etc.'Handwritten on verso: 'trusty steed, bed, etc.'
- Alan Priest, 1962; 2006.6.148; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/4 x 3 1/4 inches
- Fita (Francis O'Keeffe's Nanny), 1950; 2006.6.149; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 13/16 x 2 3/16 inches; On post-it: "Fita, woman who took care of Francis O'Keeffe throughout childhood" Stamp on back: "Vinci studio, Mar 9 1960 Infanta 310 altos"
- Francis O'Keeffe and Unidentified Woman (Possibly Fiancee), 1960; 2006.6.150; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 3 13/16 inches; Stamp on verso: "#18"
- Unidentified Woman (Possibly Francis O'Keeffe's Fiancee), 1960; 2006.6.151; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 11/16 x 3 3/4 inches; Stamp on verso: "#18"
- Unidentified Woman (Possibly Francis O'Keeffe's Fiancee), 1960; 2006.6.152; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/4 x 3 13/16 inches; on post-it: "Francis O'Keeffe (nephew to Georgia) with Cuban fiancee ~1960 (Berthica)"
- Suzanne Bloch at Carnegie Hall, 1964; 2006.6.153; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/16 x 1 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: ?Handwritten on verso: "This was taken with 70 others after I hurt my shoulder & was learning to hold a lute again. I like its shadowy feel _______ on hands even if a bit theatrical!" (____ indicates unknown word) Handwritten on post-it: "Suzanne Bloch Carnegie Hall recital Feb. 1964"
- Jim Barnett, Mid 20th Century; 2006.6.154; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso:"Jim Barnett, 823/6A"
- Catherine Klenert with Georgia O'Keeffe's Painting "Sky Above Clouds III/Above the Clouds III", after 1963; 2006.6.155; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 9/16 inches
- Frances Halden and Helen Jones with Skull, Mid 20th Century; 2006.6.156; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/8 x 4 1/4 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Longhorn Skull for Miss O'Keeffe.'Handwritten on verso: 'Longhorn Skull for Miss O'Keeffe Frances Halder and Helen Jones on the Halder's adobe walled terrace - (sun shadows through latticed roof on walls behind)' metal Stamp letters: "C706061" rubber stamp: "8"
- Ruth Claire Weintraub and Noah Sky Kelsey Lundy, circa 1970; 2006.6.157; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 9/16 x 2 9/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'without any doubts, Ruth Claire Weintraub and Noah Sky Kelsey Lundy July 1970'Handwritten on verso: 'without any doubts, Ruth Claire Weintraub and Noah Sky Kelsey Lundy July 1970'
- Unidentified Young Woman, circa 1964; 2006.6.158; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 3 9/16 inches
- Unidentified Boy, circa 1964; 2006.6.159; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 3/4 x 3 7/16 inches; Printed on recto: "Mar 64"
- Unidentified Boy, circa 1964; 2006.6.160; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 2 1/2 x 1 11/16 inches
- Unidentified Baby, circa 1964; 2006.6.161; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 3 1/2 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Jan 64, Kodachrome print
- Unidentified Man, circa 1972; 2006.6.162; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 4 3/16 x 3 1/4 inches
- Unidentified Man, 1972 October; 2006.6.163; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 4 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Abiquiu bread made in France by a China man'Handwritten on verso: 'Abiquiu bread made in France by a China man', recto boarder printed "Oct 72" with Foxprint icon
- Unidentified Man, Doris Bry and Unidentified Woman, 1950 September 11; 2006.6.164; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodacolor print and Sept. 11, 1950Stamp on verso: Kodak Sept. 11, 1950, Kodacolor print
- Ghost Ranch, 20th Century; 2006.6.165; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches
- Ghost Ranch, 20th Century; 2006.6.166; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches
- Ghost Ranch, 20th Century; 2006.6.167; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Stamp on verso: A 630
- Ghost Ranch, 20th Century; 2006.6.168; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches
- Display at Ghost Ranch, Late 20th Century; 2006.6.169; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 x 5 inches; On Verso: 'This paper manufactured by Kodak'
- Display at Ghost Ranch, Late 20th Century; 2006.6.170; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 3/8 x 4 1/4 inches; rubber Stamp along top: "POLACOLOR TYPE 108" & metal Stamp along edge: "F 812 2 3 1"
- Display at Ghost Ranch, Late 20th Century; 2006.6.171; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 3/8 x 4 1/4 inches
- Chancel of St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.173; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'The group of windows in the Chancel of St. Wulfram, Abbeville'Handwritten on verso: 'The group of windows in the Chancel of St. Wulfram, Abbeville.'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.174; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Laborece h--12 ft'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.175; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'The holy spirit 18 ft.'Handwritten on verso: 'The holy spirit h-18 ft.'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.176; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'peasarit' (?)Handwritten on verso: 'Peasant h-12 ft'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.177; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Man and Wife'Handwritten on verso: 'Man and Wife h-12ft'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.178; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 6 15/16 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'The Son'Handwritten on verso: 'The Son h-18ft.'
- Glass Windows at St. Wulfram, Abbeville, 1953; 2006.6.179; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 6 15/16 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'The Father'Handwritten on verso: 'The Father h-18 ft'
- Untitled (Leaf), after 1920; 2006.6.180; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 13/16 x 4 inches; printed: "KODAK FILM"
- Untitled (Leaf), after 1920; 2006.6.181; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 13/16 x 4 inches; Handwritten on recto: '15 1/2 x 11 1/2'Handwritten on recto: '15 1/2 x 11 1/2'
- Untitled (Leaf) Inscriptions, after 1920; 2006.6.182; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 13/16 x 4 inches; printed: "KODAK FILM"
- Untitled (Leaf) Inscriptions, after 1920; 2006.6.183; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid color photograph 3 13/16 x 4 inches; printed: "KODAK FILM"
- Land Configuration from the Sky, 1961; 2006.6.184; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: 'O'Keeffe on Pollitzer file'Stamp on verso: Kodak Nov 61, Kodachrome Print November; handwritten on verso: 'O'Keeffe in Pollitzer file'
- Land Configuration from the Sky, 1961; 2006.6.185; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: 'O'keeffe on Pollitzer file'Stamp on verso: Kodak Nov 61, Kodachrome Print; handwritten on verso: 'O'Keeffe in Pollitzer file'
- Landscape, 1971; 2006.6.186; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 7 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 76
- Landscape, 1971; 2006.6.187; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 7 inches; Stamp on verso: Kodak Mar 76
- Boats, 20th Century; 2006.6.188; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 13/16 x 4 7/8 inches; Stamp on verso: Heinz New YorkStamp on verso: HEINZ HEINZ FINE PHOTOGRAPHY 5 UNION SQ., N.Y. TEL. AL. 4-0751"
- Boats, 20th Century; 2006.6.189; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 13/16 x 4 7/8 inches; Stamp on verso: Heinz New YorkStamp on verso: HEINZ HEINZ FINE PHOTOGRAPHY 5 UNION SQ., N.Y. TEL. AL. 4-0751"
- Flowers in Vase, Marsden Hartley, after 1917; 2006.6.190; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/2 x 8 inches; Sticker on verso: University Art Museum - The University of Albuquerque - Extended Loan - oil on glass - Marsden Hartley- Flowers in Vase - 1917 - 18.4 x 16 cmLable on verso: University Art Museum - The University of Albuquerque - Extended Loan - oil on glass - Marsden Hartley- Flowers in Vase - 1917 - 18.4 x 16 cm
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1959; 2006.6.191; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: The Man on the Bridge 1959, (Venice), 65" x 52" (French measures 100 F)Handwritten on verso: The Man on the Bridge (Venice) - 1959 - 65" x 52" (French Measures 100F)
  William Einstein was a distant cousin of Stieglitz's and helped Stieglitz with An American Place gallery. Stieglitz wanted to make Einstein the successor to the Gallery. (good information about this on page 424 of Roxana Robinson's Georgia O'Keeffe: A Life biography).
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1958; 2006.6.192; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: A Foggy Day at 'Le Crotoy' 1958, (Picardie), 78" x 52" (French measures 120 F)Handwritten on verso: A Foggy Day at 'Le Crotoy (Picas del (?)) 78" x 52" (French measures 120F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1965; 2006.6.193; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: Waterloo on Brighton Pier 1965, ('Mods' against 'Rockers'), 78" x 52" (French measure 120 F)Handwritten on verso: Waterloo on Brighton Pier 1965 ("Mods "against "Rockers") 78" x 52" (french measures 120F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1962; 2006.6.194; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: Study for the 'Last Supper' 1962 (The Final Canvas 12ft x 9ft is part of triptych in St. Andre, Abbeville), 78" x 52" (French measure 120 F)Handwritten on verso: Study for "Last Supper" 1962 (The Final Canvas 12ft x 9ft is part of triptych in St. Andre, Abbeville) 78" x 52" (french measure 120F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1966; 2006.6.195; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: Glow of the Venusberg 1966, 78" x 52" (French measure 120 F), Venusberg IHandwritten on verso: Glow of the Venusberg 1966 78" x 52" (french measure 120 F) Venusberg I
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1966; 2006.6.196; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 1/8 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: On the Venusberg 1966, 78" x 52" (French measure 120 F), Venusberg IIHandwritten on verso: On The Vennsburgh 1966 78" x 52" (french measure 120F) Venusberg II
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1964; 2006.6.197; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Return From the Fields 1964, (Picardie), 65" x 52" (French measure 100 F)Handwritten on verso: Return From the Fields 1964 (Picar die) 65" x 52" (french Measure 100F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1967; 2006.6.198; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: L'Archipretre d'Abbeville 1967, 65" x 52" (French measure 100 F)Handwritten on verso: L'Archemehe d'Abbeville 1967 65" x 52" (french measure 100F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1969; 2006.6.199; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: Will Power, 65" x 52" (French measures 100 F)Handwritten on verso: Will Power 1969 65" x 52" (french measures 100F)
- Photograph of William Einstein Painting, after 1969; 2006.6.200; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: War Game 1969, 58" x 46" (French measure 80 F)Handwritten on verso: War Game 1969 58" x 46" (french measure 80F)